What...
What the hell is going on?!
A Savage.
D...
Don't!
Yet another dream about that day...
Who was that girl?
So that's the academy city-ship, Little Garden...
My home from now on.
Little Garden
This place is bigger than I thought.
We Cordially Welcome You
Kisaragi Hayato-kun
Kisaragi-kun! Yes, you, with the highest
Hundred compatibility score of all time!
Kisaragi Hayato-kun!
Where are you?
Holler if you can hear us!
That's weird.
Maybe he's on a later flight.
I guess this is it.
Um, is this where the entrance ceremony will be held?
Yeah, it is.
Wait!
Are you Kisaragi Hayato?!
What?
So you're the one with the all-time record?
Is it really him?!
He looks completely normal.
Give me your autograph!
Hayato!
I couldn't wait to see you, Hayato!
Ow, ow, ow...
What are you doing?
My name is Emile.
Emile Crossfode.
I'm also a new student here
at the Little Garden.
Let's get along, 'kay?
S-Sure.
I'm sorry, Hayato.
I shouldn't have yelled out like that.
That's right, Reitia.
Apologize.
Fritz!
I told you to stop treating me like a kid.
It's your fault for having your head
at such a perfect height.
They've been friends since they were kids.
They're really close, huh?
Y-Yeah.
You guys are pretty close yourself,
even though you just met.
Yes. It's almost like you're not both guys.
Really?
What should we do, Hayato?
I would like to welcome
all the new students here.
We're your MCs for today...
Second-year military arts
student at the Little Garden
and student council vice president,
Erica Candle.
Likewise. Liddy Steinberg.
The captain of the Little Garden,
as well as our president, Claire Harvey,
will greet you.
That's the student council president.
Yeah.
The queen, Claire Harvey.
Sorry...
Sorry we're late!
Those two...
Late for the entrance ceremony,
right off the bat?
You two sure have some nerve.
W-We're sorry!
We had gone to the airport
to pick up Kisaragi-kun.
But we couldn't find him, and then...
Enough excuses!
Kisaragi Hayato has been
right there this whole time.
Huh?
Noa Sheldon. Liu Xuemei.
There is no place in the Little Garden
for those who cannot follow the rules.
Collect your things and leave.
I... uh....
I think you're being kind of harsh here!
E-Emile?
Student council president or not,
you can't just kick them out
for making one mistake.
That's awful!
Hey!
Don't stop me, Hayato!
I can't stand people who
abuse their power like that.
Yeah, but...
You two are in no position to speak here.
W-We're sorry.
I-It's just that... I don't really think
they should be expelled just like that.
Kisaragi Hayato.
No, I will say this to everyone here.
You are not just students.
You are fledgling Slayers that will
risk their lives to fight the Savages.
On the battlefield,
a single mistake can prove fatal
and destroy an entire squadron.
It is not a matter of frequency.
Failure to follow orders will lead to death.
But there are times when
orders can prove incorrect!
That's enough, Emile Crossfode.
Claire-sama's orders are absolute. She is
the queen of our military arts department.
"Queen," my foot!
Hayato has a higher
Hundred compatibility score.
H-Hey!
Emile Crossfode, if you try
to demean her any further,
you'll be expelled, as well!
Bring it on!
Just you try—
Hey!
Very well.
As you wish, you will be expelled
along with the previous two.
Hey, stop going crazy!
Kisaragi Hayato.
Y-Yes!
Do you object to their expulsion?
Um...
Do you?
I...
I do!
Wha—
Dude!
The two girls were late because
they were looking for me,
and if that hadn't happened,
Emile wouldn't have...
Hayato...
So I know I'm in no position to say this,
but I ask that you please be lenient.
Kisaragi Hayato, know your place!
Very well.
President!
How about this, then?
Kisaragi Hayato.
I, Claire Harvey,
challenge you to a duel.
If you beat me, I will
reverse their expulsion.
We'll do this tomorrow afternoon.
The place will be the main colosseum.
H-Hold on a second. I still—
You're on!
Who asked you to decide?!
Let's do it, Hayato!
Huh?
You can definitely beat her!
Uh... Um...
Hold on...
What?
What were you thinking?
You can't just accept a duel like that.
I'm going up against the queen,
the strongest person in the Little Garden.
You'll be fine, Hayato.
I'm sure you can win.
What are you even basing that on?
It'll be fine.
Come on.
Oh.
I'll introduce you to my good friend.
Good friend?
The main technologist on the Little Garden,
the chief researcher of the Hundred.
So you're Kisaragi Hayato-kun.
My name is Charlotte Dimandius.
Call me Char.
S-Sure.
N-Nice to meet you.
Huh?
Sniff sniff sniff.
What is it?
You're from the Empire of Yamato,
but you don't smell like soy sauce.
We normally don't...
You might think she's pretty weird,
but she's actually my talented assistant.
Nice to meet you. I'm Meimei.
Nice to meet you.
And Char over here is smart enough
to be called a child prodigy.
Really?
Are you trying to insult me?
I'm actually old enough to get married, you know?
Emil—
Char, my name is Emile.
Did you forget?
Jorry aboud dat, Emile.
Hmm?
But I was surprised.
A guy who's never used Hundred before
is going to duel with Claire Harvey.
You sure get your news fast.
LiZA told me.
LiZA?
This autonomous computer that controls
everything in the Little Garden.
She can also express herself
and communicate with people.
So this is LiZA?
Exactly.
This is your Hundred.
I should explain before I give this to you.
The Hundred are the only effective weapons
against the Savage lifeforms.
However, only humans which respond
to variable stones can use them.
We call them Slayers.
The Hundred change into a ton of forms
based on who uses them.
That is where the Century Armaments,
or Hundred, get their name from.
Claire Harvey uses this.
Floating cannons that she can control at will.
A dragoon type.
She's strong, unsurprisingly.
The Hundred take different forms
and vary in their ways of fighting.
But there's only one ultimate goal:
to protect humanity.
Hayato-kun, when you take
hold of your Hundred,
you will be entrusted with
that responsibility.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Good response.
This is my Hundred.
I got an area for you to practice.
Change into your variable suit
and use it freely.
So this is a variable suit.
It's a pretty tight fit.
Yeah.
This suit also takes a different form,
depending on the person...
What are you staring at?
We're both guys. Why are you
getting all embarrassed?
Just get your Hundred out already.
S-Sure.
Take hold of your Hundred and strongly
will it to become a weapon.
Saying "Hundred On" will release it.
Got it.
Now let's give it a try.
Sure.
Hundred On.
Good job, Hayato-kun.
That's your Hundred, Flying Swallow.
It's a chevalier type.
Flying Swallow.
My Hundred.
I knew your Hundred would be cool!
All right. Me, too!
Emile,
you already have your Hundred?
Yeah.
Some stuff happened.
Hundred On.
What's that Hundred?
This is the Arms Shroud.
My innocence type is a bit special.
Innocence type?
In any event, the duel is tomorrow.
We don't have time.
So we're going to have a trial by fire.
Fire.
That's pretty impressive, Hayato!
You're already able to put up
an energy barrier!
I wasn't even...
Wait, Emile!
Who just attacks a person
out of nowhere like that?!
The student council president
won't go easy on you!
Y-You moron!
Huh?
Ow...
Awesome! That was awesome, Hayato!
You can win! There's no question!
Y-Yeah, right!
I came up with a plan.
Plan?
As such,
I'm going to ride you hard!
W-Wait!
Good job hanging in there, Hayato.
Now you'll definitely win tomorrow's duel.
I'm not sure it'll go so well.
Huh?
Shoot. It's my sister.
Karen
I forgot I'd promised to go to the hospital
right after the entrance ceremony.
Hospital?
Is your sister hospitalized?
Yeah. She's not exactly healthy.
I came to the Little Garden on the condition
that she'd get cutting-edge medical care.
Sorry, Emile. Head back to the dorm on your own.
S-Sure.
I'm sorry, Karen!
My bad!
Hey, could you forgive me already?
In that case...
What am I gonna do with you?
I forgive you.
Oh, yeah.
How was the entrance ceremony?
W-Well, you see...
A lot happened.
Come in.
Torpedoes!
Sorry to interrupt, Karen-chan,
but it's almost the end of visiting hours.
What? Already?
I... I'm sorry.
I'll be leaving now.
You perv.
What?
You're getting all flustered
looking at Miharu's boobs.
S-Stupid! I'm not...
It got pretty late.
The lights are on?
Huh?
Emile?
Hayato...
Get out!
W-Wait!
You moron! Don't—
Oh, are you up, Hayato?
Emile...
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
What was that for?!
It's your fault for getting up so suddenly.
A-Are you stupid?
I just panicked because I was resting my head on another guy's lap.
This is all your fault to begin with.
You just waltzed right in.
That's why this happened.
"Waltzed right in," you say?
This is my room, you know?
Wait. Why are you in my room, anyway?
I didn't say?
We're roommates.
Huh?
What?
There you have it.
Now take off your uniform.
I'll sew your badge back on.
Are you okay?
I can do that myself.
You have an important duel tomorrow.
Just let me handle it—
Ow.
See.
We need to take care of that now.
Huh?
H-Hayato.
You can't just...
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
It wasn't that big of a deal...
It's just how I am.
I got mixed up in a Savage
attack a long time ago.
Now, when I see someone get hurt,
I just have to do something.
Hayato...
Thank you.
Are you ready?
As much as I can be.
In that case, have at you.
Hundred On.
The duel between the queen, Claire Harvey,
and the new student,
Kisaragi Hayato, shall begin.
Now, Kisaragi Hayato,
show me how strong you are!
The Invincible Queen